<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Scottsdale, AZ Web Designer and Developer]]></title><description><![CDATA[I am a web designer and developer located in Scottsdale, Arizona. I have 14 years experience working with marketing, advertising and interactive design agencies]]></description><link>http://savellem.com</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 23:51:35 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[Plexus Worldwide Digital Redesign and Rebranding]]></title><description><![CDATA[Role UI/UX Designer Company Plexus Worldwide LLC Industry Multi-Level Marketing Project Deliverables Design System, Ecommerce Store…]]></description><link>http://savellem.com/a-peek-into/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://savellem.com/a-peek-into/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Role&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;UI/UX Designer&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Company&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Plexus Worldwide LLC&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Industry&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Multi-Level Marketing&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Project Deliverables&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Design System, Ecommerce Store, Replicated Site Builder, Admin Dashboard, Email Templating, Digital Branding, Marketing Landing Pages, Contest Web Applications, Custom Zendesk Theme, Custom Sharepoint Theme&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Tools/Technology&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Angular, Node.js, Bootstrap, Metalsmith, Javascript, HTML, CSS, Sketch, Abstract, Adobe Creative Suite&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the first digital designer hired to the marketing team, I lead 3 consecutive redesigns of plexusworldwide.com. This includes a custom ecommerce store, ambassador replicated site builder, back office dashboard and marketing landing pages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I helped develop an atomic design system in both Sketch and Angular components based on feedback from A/B user testing, cognitive walkthroughs and data analysis. I have also designed and developed landing pages, contest web applications, auto responder email templating systems, ZenDesk and Sharepoint theming, Custom Wordpress themes and plugins.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>